webdesigntunes.com 2018-08-21

# Privacy Policy of mhthemes.com

## Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

  *     * ### Analytics

      * ### Google Analytics with anonymized IP

Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data

    * ### Contacting the User

      * ### Contact form

Personal Data: email address, first name, last name and website

    * ### Displaying content from external platforms

      * ### Gravatar 

Personal Data: email address and Usage Data

      * ### YouTube video widget

Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data

    * ### Interaction with external social networks and platforms

      * ### Facebook Like button and social widgets

Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data

    * ### Managing contacts and sending messages

      * ### MailChimp

Personal Data: email address

    * ### Registration and authentication

      * ### Direct registration

Personal Data: email address, first name and last name

## Further information about Personal Data

  *     * ### FastSpring

FastSpring is a reliable and authorized reseller of software and other digital products with focus on safe, secure internet sales and fulfillment. When you decide to purchase products from this website, you'll be forwarded to the website from FastSpring for the purchase process and order fulfillment. For more information please refer to the [privacy policy](https://fastspring.com/privacy/) from FastSpring.

    * ### Google Fonts (Google Inc.)

Google Fonts is a typeface visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages. Personal data collected: Usage data and various types of data as specified in the [privacy policy](https://www.google.it/intl/policies/privacy/) of the service. Please refer to this page for more information: [Google Fonts API](https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq#what_does_using_the_google_fonts_api_mean_for_the_privacy_of_my_users).

    * ### Additional information

Data protection is a high priority for the management of the Array Internet GmbH. The use of this website is possible without any indication of personal data; however, if you want to use special enterprise services via our website, processing of personal data could become necessary. If the processing of personal data is necessary and there is no statutory basis for such processing, we generally obtain consent from you. Please refer to our detailed [privacy policy](https://www.iubenda.com/privacy-policy/51960644/legal) for more information.

    * ### 1&1 Hosting

1&1 collects and processes data solely for the purposes of website hosting as well as for the technical optimization of the website. The date and time of access, URL of the referring website, retrieved file, amount of sent data, browser type and version, operating system, type of device used and your IP address in anonymised form are recorded. The storage period is 7 days. For more information, please see the [1&1 Privacy Policy](https://hosting.1und1.de/terms-gtc/terms-privacy/).

    * ### aMember Membership Software

This website uses aMember to provide a sophisticated and secure membership platform to its users. When you create an account on this website, you'll be asked to provide your email, name and preferred username. For security purposes also your IP address is being collected by the system. In addition session cookies are being set. These cookies are required by the system in order to provide services for the customer.

  *     * ### Owner and Data Controller

Array Internet GmbH   
Kastor Tower – 20th Floor   
Platz der Einheit 1   
60327 Frankfurt am Main   
Germany

**Owner contact email:** info@mhthemes.com
